Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco Papers
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Writings, 1919-1997 (Box 109-119)
  - Works about Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco by others, 1925-1997
    - Articles
      - Colacicchi, Luigi. "Prestiti e affiti" musicali. Musica, pp. 135-140, Laid in: letter from Colacicchi to Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco, 1944 December 5 (Box-folder 119/2)
      - Gatti, Guido M. Musicisti italiani: Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. La critica musicale, vol. 1, no. 10-11,(October-November 1918), pp. 197-206 (Box-folder 119/3)
      - Gatti, Guido M. Ricordo di Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Estratto annuario accademia nazionala di S. Cecilia, (December 1969), 10 p. (Box-folder 119/3)
      - Gilardino, Angelo. Ricordi di Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Strumenti and musica, vol. 21, no. 4, (1968), pp. 30-32, Laid in: correspondence with Pietro Castelnuovo-Tedesco, 1995 (Box-folder 119/4)
      - Gilardino, Angelo. Un fiorentino a Beverly Hills. Seicorde, vol 10, no. 53, (September-October 1995), pp. 24-33 (Box-folder 119/4)
      - Grossman, Emery. Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco: contemporary composer. Temple Israel Light, pp. 10-11 (Box-folder 119/5)
      - Liuzzi, Fernando. Un articolo di solaria, quaranta anni fa Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Portico d'Ottavia, no. 7-8, (February-April 1968), pp. 53-58 (Box-folder 119/6)
      - Liuzzi, Fernando. Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Italien Sonderheft des Anbruch, vol. 7, (August-September 1925), pp. 408-440 (Box-folder 119/6)
      - Lubin, Ernest. A neglected Impressionist: Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Clavier, vol. 10, no. 2, (February 1971), pp. 29-31 (Box-folder 119/7)
      - Miscellaneous articles, 1939-1947, 1958-1967, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 119/8-9)
      - Purcell, Ronald C. Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco and the guitar. Guitar Review, no. 37, (1972), pp. 2-4 (Box-folder 119/10)
      - Reeves, David. The piano works of Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Piano and Keyboard, no. 176, (October 1995), pp. 29-33, Laid in: correspondence with Pietro Castelnuovo-Tedesco, 1995 (Box-folder 119/11)
      - Rossi, Nick. The choral masterpieces of Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. The Choral Journal, (November 1976), pp. 5-8 (Box-folder 119/12)
      - Rossi, Nick. A musical portrait of Italy. Keyboard Classics, (March-April 1982), pp. 10-12 (Box-folder 119/12)
      - Scalin, Burton. Old Testament works by Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco. Tatzlil, vol. 9, no. 10, (1976), pp. 19-24 (Box-folder 119/13)
      - Scalin, Burton. Some biblically-inspired and liturgical compositions of Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco, [circa 1975?] (Box-folder 119/13)
      - Takahashi, Isao, 1954, 1968, unidentified dates, 6 articles from various Japanese publications (Box-folder 119/14-15)
    - Miscellany
      - International Castelnuovo-Tedesco Society, 1973-1985, Correspondence and publications (Box-folder 119/16)
      - List of recordings, undated, Principally photocopied catalog cards (Box-folder 119/17)
      - Rossi, Nick, undated, Program notes (Box-folder 119/18)
- Correspondence, 1908-1998 (Box 120-138)
  - General correspondence, 1922-1998
    - Abreu, Sergio, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 120/1)
    - Afshar, Lily, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 120/2)
    - Albersheim, Erna, 1948-1967 (Box-folder 120/3)
    - Albersheim, Gerhard, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 120/4)
    - Almeida, Laurindo, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 120/5)
    - Barber, Samuel, 1940s (Box-folder 120/6)
    - Barbosa-Lima, Carlo, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 120/7)
    - Barbirolli, John and Evelyn Rothschild, 1941-1967 (Box-folder 120/8)
    - Barr, Cyrilla, 1997 (Box-folder 120/9)
    - Behrend, Siegfried, 1952-1990 (Box-folder 120/10-11)
    - Bennett, Lynette, 1997 (Box-folder 120/12)
    - Berenson, Bernard, 1934-1941 (Box-folder 120/13)
    - Berman, Judith, 1978-1979, 1994 (Box-folder 120/14)
    - Bernstein, Leonard, 1955 (Box-folder 120/15)
    - Bianchi-Banclinelli, R., 1946 (Box-folder 120/16)
    - Black, Richard, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 120/17)
    - Blanchard, Henry, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 120/18)
    - Bloch, Ernest, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 120/19)
    - Blumenthal, Daniel, 1994 (Box-folder 120/20)
    - Bocchi, Sauro, 1995 (Box-folder 120/21)
    - Bocchino, Alberto, 1994 (Box-folder 120/22)
    - Bonaguri, Piero, 1995 (Box-folder 120/23)
    - Bonucci, Arturo, 1997 (Box-folder 120/24)
    - Botto, Andrea, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 120/25)
    - Boudounis, Evangelos, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 120/26)
    - Bronkhorst, Julia, 1998 (Box-folder 120/27)
    - Brostoff, Neal, 1994 (Box-folder 120/28)
    - Browning, Winslow, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 120/29)
    - Bucci, Carlo Alberto, 1995 (Box-folder 120/30)
    - Cagli, Corrado, undated (Box-folder 121/1)
    - Caporali, Rodolfo, 1995 (Box-folder 121/2)
    - Capra, Marco, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 121/3)
    - Casella, Alfredo, 1945 (Box-folder 121/4)
    - Charnofsky, Jordan, 1997 (Box-folder 121/5)
    - Chertok, Pearl, 1972 (Box-folder 121/6)
    - Clurman, Judith, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 121/7)
    - Coen, Massimo, 1996 (Box-folder 121/8)
    - Colacicchi, Giovanni, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 121/9)
    - Condolence letters after Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco's death, 1968 (Box-folder 128/25)
    - Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague, 1938 (Box-folder 121/10)
    - Correspondence from various guitarists, 1953-1971, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 128/26)
    - Correspondence logs by Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco, 1947-1968 (Box-folder 128/27)
    - Costa, Maria Lucia, 1997 (Box-folder 121/11)
    - Crowson, Gerald, 1997 (Box-folder 121/12)
    - Dallapiccola, Luigi, 1945 (Box-folder 121/13)
    - D’Amico, Fedele, 1969 (Box-folder 121/14)
    - D'Annunzio, Gabriele, 1929 (Box-folder 121/15)
    - Dickstein, Marcia, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 121/16)
    - Dilocco, Francesco, see Bucci, Carlo Alberto
    - Downes, Olin, 1940, 1950 (Box-folder 121/17)
    - Duarte, John, 1967-1978 (Box-folder 121/18)
    - Dunham, Katherine, 1948 (Box-folder 121/19)
    - Durante, Sergio, 1997 (Box-folder 121/20)
    - Enos, Joseph, 1954 (Box-folder 121/21)
    - Escovado, Robin, 1995 (Box-folder 121/22)
    - Estarellas, Gabriel, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 121/23)
    - Farrell, Eileen, 1964 (Box-folder 121/24)
    - Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 121/25)
    - Fisk, Elliot, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 121/26)
    - Fogo, Byron, 1994 (Box-folder 121/27)
    - Ford, John Scott, 1994 (Box-folder 121/28)
    - Frampton, Robert, 1997 (Box-folder 121/29)
    - Gavazzeni, G., 1954-1958 (Box-folder 121/30)
    - Gelenbe, Deniz Arman, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 121/31)
    - Gilardino, Angelo, 1967-1995 (Box-folder 122/1-3)
    - Gordon, Eric, 1997 (Box-folder 122/4)
    - Gray, Dorothy Landis, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 122/5)
    - Green, Noreen, 1995 (Box-folder 122/6)
    - Grey, Madeleine, undated (Box-folder 122/7)
    - Gui, Vittorio, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 122/8)
    - Heifetz, Jascha, 1926-1944 (Box-folder 122/9)
    - Herbst, Jerry, 1945 (Box-folder 122/10)
    - Higham, Peter, 1975-1981, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 122/11-12)
    - Kahan, Sylvia, 1993 (Box-folder 122/13)
    - Kipnis, Igor, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 122/14)
    - Koonce, Frank, 1995 (Box-folder 122/15)
    - Kotzia, Eleftheria, 1994 (Box-folder 122/16)
    - Labroca, Mario, 1949-1957 (Box-folder 123/1)
    - Lavry, Marc, 1954 (Box-folder 123/2)
    - Lehmann, Azumi, 1996 (Box-folder 123/3)
    - Lehmann, Lotte, 1952 (Box-folder 123/4)
    - Leinsdorf, Erich, 1955 (Box-folder 123/5)
    - Leisner, David, 1995 (Box-folder 123/6)
    - Lemieux, Robert, 1983 (Box-folder 123/7)
    - Levitch, Leon, 1982-1995 (Box-folder 123/8)
    - Litante, Judith, 1955 (Box-folder 123/9)
    - Liuzzi, Fernando and Paula, 1927, undated (Box-folder 123/10)
    - Liuzzi Archive, 1972 (Box-folder 123/11)
    - Lloyd-Webber, Julian, 1995 (Box-folder 123/12)
    - Loria, Arturo, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 123/13)
    - Louisville Symphony Orchestra, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 123/14)
    - Lubin, Ernest, 1949-1975 (Box-folder 123/15)
    - Ma, Yo-Yo, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 123/16)
    - Maggio Musicale, 1949-1967 (Box-folder 123/17)
    - Maiorca, Giuseppe, 1997 (Box-folder 123/18)
    - Maldi, Lamberto, 1971 (Box-folder 123/19)
    - Mallarme Chamber Players, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 123/20)
    - Margaria, Guido, 1971 (Box-folder 123/21)
    - Mariano, Nicky, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 123/22)
    - Mastik, Martin, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 123/23)
    - Mastrocinque, Mariadele, 1998 (Box-folder 123/24)
    - Matsuda, Jiro, 1967-1980 (Box-folder 123/25)
    - Mayer, Abe, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 123/26)
    - Menotti, Giam Carlo, 1956 (Box-folder 123/27)
    - Mercado, Andrés, 1994 (Box-folder 123/28)
    - Merkin Concert Hall, 1995 (Box-folder 123/29)
    - Mitropoukos, Dmitri, 1940 (Box-folder 123/30)
    - Moldenhauer, Hans, 1958-1980 (Box-folder 123/31-32)
    - Molinari, Jorge, 1972 (Box-folder 123/33)
    - Monteux, Pierre, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 123/34)
    - Miscellany, 1922-1928, 1940-1952, 1961-1966, 1979-1996, undated (Box-folder 128/28-29)
    - Mundi, Charles, 1957 (Box-folder 123/35)
    - Mysior, Ilana, 1976 (Box-folder 123/36)
    - Napoli, Jacopo, 1950-1967 (Box-folder 124/1)
    - Nathan, Robert, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 124/2)
    - National Jewish Music Council, 1965 (Box-folder 124/3)
    - Nestor, Gregg, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 124/4)
    - Nixon, Marni, 1972, 1994 (Box-folder 124/5)
    - Orselli, Cesare, 1977-1995 (Box-folder 124/6)
    - Otero, Corazon, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 124/7)
    - Pagliarini, Maurizio, 1996 (Box-folder 124/8)
    - Parigi, Angelo, 1940 (Box-folder 124/9)
    - Parkening, Christopher, 1966 (Box-folder 124/10)
    - Passigli, Franco, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 124/11)
    - Perlman, Itzhak, 1993 (Box-folder 124/12)
    - Pisani, Michael V., 1994-1995 (Box-folder 124/13)
    - Pizzetti, Ildebrando, 1940-1947 (Box-folder 124/14)
    - Ponsillo, Cinzia, 1996 (Box-folder 124/15)
    - Previn, Andre, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 124/16)
    - Purcell, Ron, 1969-1996 (Box-folder 124/17)
    - Ramos, Manuel Lopez, 1966 (Box-folder 124/18)
    - Rawitz, Benjamin, 1990 (Box-folder 124/19)
    - Reed, H. Owen, 1969 (Box-folder 124/20)
    - Rosselli, Amelia, 1936-1953 (Box-folder 124/21)
    - Rossi, Nick, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 125/1-7)
    - Rossi, Nick, 1967-1993, undated (Box-folder 126/1-13)
    - Rota, Nino, 1939-1978 (Box-folder 127/1)
    - Sacchetti, Arturo, 1972 (Box-folder 127/2)
    - Sacjs, Harvey, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 127/3)
    - Sagra Musicale Umbra, 1957 (Box-folder 127/4)
    - Scalin, Burton, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 127/5)
    - Scardovi, Stefano, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 127/6)
    - Schonberg, Harold C., 1963 (Box-folder 127/7)
    - Segovia, Andrés, 1950s-1980s, RESTRICTED (Box 160-161)
    - Segovia, Emilita, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 127/8)
    - Sellers, Michael, 1997 (Box-folder 127/9)
    - Sergo, Emanuel, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 127/10)
    - Sherman, Robert, 1995 (Box-folder 127/11)
    - Siegel, Alvin, 1969 (Box-folder 127/12)
    - Slonimsky, Nicolas, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 127/13)
    - Snijders, Trins, 1993 (Box-folder 127/14)
    - Sohayda, Jan, 1993 (Box-folder 127/15)
    - Solow, Davida and Jeffery, 1996 (Box-folder 127/16)
    - Soltes, Auraham, 1970 (Box-folder 127/17)
    - Spaulding, Albert, 1937-1942 (Box-folder 127/18)
    - Spivakosky, Tossy, 1942-1953 (Box-folder 127/19)
    - Stein, Herman, 1957 (Box-folder 127/20)
    - Steinberg, William, 1959 (Box-folder 127/21)
    - Stevens, Delores, 1995 (Box-folder 127/22)
    - Stokowski, Leopold, 1945 (Box-folder 127/23)
    - Strozzi, Memmi, 1939-1950, undated (Box-folder 127/24-32)
    - Swing, Raymond Gram, 1940 (Box-folder 127/33)
    - Szigeti, Joseph, 1945 (Box-folder 127/34)
    - Takahashi, Isao, 1953-1969 (Box-folder 128/1)
    - Tallini, Arturo, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 128/2)
    - Thiel, Jean, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 128/3)
    - Tinturin, Glenn, 1994 (Box-folder 128/4)
    - Torsiglieri, Massimiliano, 1995 (Box-folder 128/5)
    - Toscanini, Arturo, 1929-1949 (Box-folder 128/6)
    - Toscanini, Elaine, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 128/7)
    - Toscanini, Walter, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 128/8)
    - Trompetter, Amy, 1995 (Box-folder 128/9)
    - Tulan, Fredrik, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 128/10)
    - UCLA Department of Theater Arts, 1962, 1971 (Box-folder 128/11)
    - Vannucci, Marcello, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 128/12)
    - Vlad, Roman, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 128/13)
    - Waterhouse, John, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 128/14)
    - Waxman, Franz, 1964 (Box-folder 128/15)
    - Weber, Roland von, undated (Box-folder 128/16)
    - Weiss, Sidney, 1993 (Box-folder 128/17)
    - Westby, James, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 128/18)
    - Williams, John, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 128/19)
    - Wolfram, William, 1995 (Box-folder 128/20)
    - Woodfull-Harris, Douglas, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 128/21)
    - Yates, Stanley, 1995 (Box-folder 128/22)
    - Zeisl, Eugene, 1961 (Box-folder 128/23)
    - Zigante, Frederic, 1995 (Box-folder 128/24)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 128/30)
  - Family correspondence, 1908-1984
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Amedeo and Noemi
      - Mario to Amedeo and Noemi, 1911-1940 (Box-folder 129/1-41)
      - Mario to Amedeo and Noemi, 1941-1947 (Box-folder 130/1-46)
      - Amedeo to Mario, 1939-1947 (Box-folder 131/1-69)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Clara
      - Mario to Clara, 1937-1941, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 136/8-20)
      - Clara to Mario, 1940-1942, undated (Box-folder 137/1-7)
      - Clara, Pietro, and/or Lorenzo to Mario, 1940 November (Box-folder 137/8)
      - Others to Clara, 1939-1970 (Box-folder 137/9-11)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Lorenzo
      - Lorenzo to Mario, 1940-1941, 1964 (Box-folder 136/6)
      - Unidentified letter about Lorenzo, 1935 August (Box-folder 136/7)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Pietro
      - Mario and Clara to Pietro, 1938-1953 (Box-folder 132/1-19)
      - Mario and Clara to Pietro, 1954-1942 (Box-folder 133/1-32)
      - Pietro to Mario and Clara, 1944-1947 (Box-folder 134/1-14)
      - Pietro to Mario and Clara, 1948-1966 (Box-folder 135/1-11)
      - Pietro to Mario and Clara, undated, circa 1940s? (Box-folder 135/12)
      - Pietro to Mario and Clara, undated, circa 1948-1950? (Box-folder 136/1)
      - Pietro to Mario and Clara, undated (Box-folder 136/2)
      - Pietro to Clara, 1969, 1976, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 136/3)
      - Pietro to others, 1942 (Box-folder 136/4)
      - Others to Pietro, 1940-1946, undated (Box-folder 136/5)
    - Other family members and friends
      - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Adriana
        - Mario to Adriana, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 138/1-9)
      - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Guido
        - Mario to Guido, 1941-1959 (Box-folder 138/10-28)
      - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Guido and Adriana
        - Guido and Adriana to Mario, 1940-1948 (Box-folder 138/29)
      - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Lisbeth, see Miller, Lisbeth
      - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Ugo
        - Ugo to Mario, 1939-1952, RESTRICTED until 2020 (Box-folder 138/30-31)
      - Emilia
        - Emilia to Mario, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 138/32)
      - Giuseppina, Nonna
        - Nonna to Clara, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 138/33-34)
      - Lilly
        - Lilly to Mario, 1940-1946 (Box-folder 138/35)
      - Marta
        - Marta to Mario, 1959-1941 (Box-folder 138/36)
      - Michele
        - Michele to Mario, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 138/33)
      - Miller, Lisbeth
        - Lisbeth to Mario, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 138/38)
      - Other family members or friends
        - Mario to others, 1963 (Box-folder 138/39)
        - Others to Mario, 1908, 1940-1947, 1961 (Box-folder 138/40)
      - Stone, Mr. and Mrs. Samuel
        - Mario to Stone family, 1954-1957 (Box-folder 138/41)
- Business Files, 1915-1997 (Box 139-142)
  - ABC Concerts
    - 1994-1996 (Box-folder 139/1)
  - Affiliated Musicians, Inc.
    - 1952-1953 (Box-folder 139/2)
  - Agenzia International Concerti
    - 1952 (Box-folder 139/3)
  - American Music Edition
    - 1954-1959 (Box-folder 139/4)
  - ASCAP
    - Correspondence, 1940-1995 (Box-folder 139/5-6)
    - Payment records, 1951-1967 (Box-folder 139/7-9)
    - Payment stubs, 1965-1996 (Box-folder 139/10)
    - Writer Performance Records, 1952, 1956-1958, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 139/11)
  - Associated Music Publishers
    - 1940-1971 (Box-folder 139/12)
  - BBC
    - 1961 (Box-folder 139/13)
  - Becker / Fehr
    - 1916-1919 (Box-folder 139/14)
  - Belwin Mills
    - 1975-1979 (Box-folder 139/15)
  - Musicverlag Anton J. Benjamin
    - 1972-1979 (Box-folder 139/16)
  - Bèrben
    - 1963-1966 (Box-folder 139/17-18)
  - C.C. Birchard and Co.
    - 1945-1949 (Box-folder 139/19)
  - Boosey and Hawkes
    - 1941-1959 (Box-folder 139/20)
  - Bote and Bock
    - 1957-1995 (Box-folder 139/21)
  - Bruzzichelli, Aldo
    - 1967-1995 (Box-folder 139/22)
  - Cal Arts
    - 1963-1967 (Box-folder 140/1)
  - Carrisch
    - 1931-1939 (Box-folder 140/2)
  - Chanterelle
    - 1992-1993 (Box-folder 140/3)
  - J. and W. Chester
    - 1921-1991 (Box-folder 140/4)
  - Collins Jr., W. Ovid
    - 1972-1994 (Box-folder 140/5)
  - Columbia Pictures
    - 1946 (Box-folder 140/6)
  - Crystal Records
    - 1994-1997 (Box-folder 140/7)
  - Curci
    - 1927 (Box-folder 140/8)
  - Delkas
    - 1943-1946 (Box-folder 140/9)
  - Editions Orphée
    - 1988 (Box-folder 140/10)
  - Elkan
    - 1949-1959, 1992 (Box-folder 140/11)
  - EMI
    - 1991-1992 (Box-folder 140/12)
  - Encore Consultants
    - 1994-1996 (Box-folder 140/13)
  - Eschig
    - 1965-1971 (Box-folder 140/14)
  - Carl Fischer
    - 1931-1973 (Box-folder 140/15)
  - Forlivesi
    - 1915-1967 (Box-folder 140/16)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1995 (Box-folder 140/17-18)
    - Financial documents, 1916-1976 (Box-folder 140/19)
  - Galaxy Music
    - 1950-1964 (Box-folder 141/1)
    - Contracts, 1940-1955 (Box-folder 141/2)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 141/3)
  - General Music
    - 1967-1976 (Box-folder 141/4)
  - Mitchell Gertz
    - 1946-1952 (Box-folder 141/5)
  - H. W. Gray
    - 1951-1953 (Box-folder 141/6)
  - Hebrew Union College
    - 1962-1964 (Box-folder 141/7)
  - Klauss Heymann
    - 1992-1995 (Box-folder 141/8)
  - Leeds Music Co.
    - 1949-1964 (Box-folder 141/9)
  - Lyra Music Co.
    - 1992-1993 (Box-folder 141/10)
  - Edward B. Marks
    - 1958-1966 (Box-folder 141/11)
  - McLaughlin and Reilly Co.
    - 1968 (Box-folder 141/12)
  - Mercury
    - 1948-1959 (Box-folder 141/13)
  - Michigan State University
    - 1959 (Box-folder 141/14)
  - MGM
    - 1941-1942 (Box-folder 141/15)
  - Mills Music, Inc.
    - 1950-1967 (Box-folder 141/16)
  - Miscellaneous contracts
    - 1946-1965 (Box-folder 141/17)
  - Monstrous Movie Music
    - 1998 (Box-folder 141/18)
  - Morini, Albert
    - 1937-1940 (Box-folder 141/19)
  - Edwin H. Morris and Co.
    - 1953-1956 (Box-folder 141/20)
  - Musikstrasse
    - 1994 (Box-folder 141/21)
  - Popular Pictures, Inc.
    - 1945 (Box-folder 142/1)
  - RAI (Radia Italiana)
    - 1948-1952 (Box-folder 142/2)
  - Record companies
    - 1952-1978 (Box-folder 142/3)
  - Ricordi
    - 1925-1938 (Box-folder 142/4)
    - Contracts, 1940-1961 (Box-folder 142/5)
    - Correspondence, 1939-1997 (Box-folder 142/6-9)
    - Miscellany, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 142/10)
  - Rubinstein-Lambro
    - 1964-1970 (Box-folder 142/11)
  - La Scala
    - 1954-1963 (Box-folder 142/12)
  - G. Schirmer
    - 1951-1971 (Box-folder 142/13)
  - Schott
    - 1932-1934 (Box-folder 142/14)
  - Senart
    - 1926 (Box-folder 142/15)
  - Società italiana degli autori ed editori
    - 1924-1933, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 142/16-17)
  - Suvini Zerboni, Inc.
    - 1968-1994 (Box-folder 142/18)
  - Tarpinian / Alexander Bronde / Israeli Music Publishing
    - 1951-1979 (Box-folder 142/19)
  - Transcontinental Music
    - 1980-1995 (Box-folder 142/20)
  - Twentieth Century Fox
    - 1949 (Box-folder 142/21)
  - Universal Edition
    - 1926-1939, 1972, 1994 (Box-folder 142/22)
  - UPA Cartoons
    - 1956 (Box-folder 142/23)
  - Weaner-Levant
    - 1942-1947 (Box-folder 142/24)
- Photographs, circa 1900-1970s (Box 143-146)
  - before 1900 and 1900s, 7 photographs (Box-folder 143/1)
  - 1901, 1 photograph (Box-folder 143/2)
  - 1908, 6 photographs (Box-folder 143/3)
  - 1910, 3 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/4)
  - 1916, 1 photograph (Box-folder 143/5)
  - 1921, 4 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/6)
  - 1921, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/1)
  - 1924, 1 photograph (Box-folder 143/7)
  - 1925, 11 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/8)
  - 1926, 3 photographs (Box-folder 143/9)
  - 1928, 3 photographs (Box-folder 143/10)
  - 1930s, 16 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/11)
  - 1930s, 8 photographs, negatives; Includes: J. Heifetz and C. Cui (Box-folder 143/12)
  - 1931, 1 photograph-postcard, negatives (Box-folder 143/13)
  - 1932, 10 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/14)
  - 1933, 9 photographs; Includes: A. Toscanini (Box-folder 143/15)
  - 1934, Negatives (Box-folder 143/16)
  - 1935, 5 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/17)
  - 1936, 2 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/18)
  - 1937, Negatives (Box-folder 143/19)
  - 1938, 5 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/20)
  - 1939, 14 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/21)
  - 1938 or 1940, 1 photograph, negatives (Box-folder 143/22)
  - 1940s, 19 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/23)
  - 1940s, 8 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 143/24)
  - 1940, 5 photographs (Box-folder 144/1)
  - 1941, 3 photographs (Box-folder 144/2)
  - 1946, 6 photographs (Box-folder 144/3)
  - 1947, 10 photographs (Box-folder 144/4)
  - 1948, 1 photograph (Box-folder 144/5)
  - 1949, 2 photographs (Box-folder 144/6)
  - 1950s, 28 photographs (Box-folder 144/7)
  - 1950, 3 photographs (Box-folder 144/8)
  - 1950, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/2)
  - 1954, 3 photographs (Box-folder 144/9)
  - 1955, 22 photographs, negatives; Includes: I. Stravinsky, W. Gieseking (Box-folder 144/10)
  - 1956, 11 photographs (Box-folder 144/11)
  - 1957, 7 photographs (Box-folder 144/12)
  - 1957?, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/3)
  - 1958, 12 photographs (Box-folder 144/13)
  - 1958, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/4)
  - 1958, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/5)
  - 1959, 6 photographs (Box-folder 144/14)
  - 1959, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/6)
  - 1960s, 27 photographs, negatives (Box-folder 144/15)
  - 1960, 6 photographs (Box-folder 144/16)
  - 1968, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/7)
  - 1968, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/8)
  - 1970s, 4 photographs (Box-folder 144/17)
  - Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco, undated, 3 photographs, negatives; Includes: portrait (Box-folder 144/18)
  - Noemi Castelnuovo-Tedesco, undated, 8 photographs (Box-folder 144/19)
  - Op. 98: Aucassin et Nicolette, 12 photographs (Box-folder 144/20)
  - Op. 172: The song of songs, 14 photographs (Box-folder 144/21)
  - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, 24 photographs; Possibly from the premiere (Box-folder 145/1)
  - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act I, 12 photographs; Possibly from the premiere (Box-folder 145/2)
  - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act II, 21 photographs; Possibly from the premiere (Box-folder 145/3)
  - Op. 181: The merchant of Venice, Act III, 16 photographs; Possibly from the premiere (Box-folder 145/4)
  - Unidentified, circa early 1900s, Orchestra, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/9)
  - Unidentified, circa early 1900s, Orchestra, 1 photograph (Box-folder 146/10)
  - Unidentified and/or undated, 1952, Stages and costumes, 28 photographs (Box-folder 145/5)
  - Unidentified and/or undated, Negatives (Box-folder 145/6)
  - Unidentified and/or undated, 29 photographs; Includes: N. Rossi, A. Gilardino, S. Behrend, A. Schweitzer (Box-folder 145/7)
  - Unidentified and/or undated, 13 photographs (Box-folder 145/8)
- Programs, 1909-1995 (Box 147-152)
  - Programs by date, 1909-1995
    - 1909-1929 (Box-folder 147/1-9)
    - 1930-1940 (Box-folder 148/1-8)
    - 1941-1959, 1960s (Box-folder 149/1-10)
    - 1960-1970 (Box-folder 150/1-7)
    - 1971-1989 (Box-folder 151/1-6)
    - 1990-1995, undated (Box-folder 152/1-4)
  - Programs by performer or subject, 1929-1995